But
I have one question
Yeah, what?
What my mother wanted to say that day
What does that mean?
Can you talk to me?
It's no big deal
Mom has work too
Because it happens like this, somehow
You probably wanted to make excuses.
I came at the right time
Even once
I was going to see you
Wait a minute
What is this?
open it
Baby
Isn’t this so pretty?
Yeah, it's pretty
Then I have this as a birthday present.
Can't you buy it for me?
A long time ago, he told me
You once asked me to buy you this
At that time, if you buy me shoes
He ran away so I couldn't buy it for him.
There's no need to worry about that anymore
and
You own this house
100% responsibility for divorce
Because I have it
It's right for you to own this house.
I'll find another house
Now you can come here and live comfortably.
In the meantime, to yourself
I did a lot of things I couldn't do
I'm sorry I couldn't make you happy
Forget about the ugly me
I met a good person
I hope you become happy again
Minwoo and Minjun
Mom and Grandpa's Words
You have to listen carefully, okay?
- yes!
- Yes
Dad will come up every weekend
Even if you miss me, hold on tight
yes
Come on, let's hug
Oh my, my sons
Father, it must be difficult
Please take care of me
Take care of your health
draw
don't worry
You too
Be careful not to get tired
yes
Yeah, don't worry
Have a nice trip
it happened somehow
I'll solve it
Just trust me
yes
Well, don't push yourself too hard.
Come with me on the weekend
Let's solve them one by one
Okay
Then I'll go
Father, I will come back
Draw it, go quickly.
Minwoo, Minjun, I’m going to dad.
- Dad
- Dad, don't go.
I have to go
I'll come back on my day off
yes, you are watching
this jacket
It's not too thin so it's not mushy.
Also, not too thick, just in the middle.
So
If you wear it over a suit...
Clean and luxurious
Can you see it?
Without disturbing the shoulder line
Hold this line
No, the fit
Isn’t it too much of an art?
Are you wearing size 55?
Uh, right
The waist line like this
It's slightly in there
Your body looks a little slimmer
Song Yena, she
no, i did this morning
Looking at the schedule
What I thought was strange
Song Yena, she
As prime time main show host
It's up
So, no, I
How did he get this position?
I was thinking about that
Just...
Could he...
Managing Director Seo Prime Time
Just because they gave it to me
Didn’t you just pass over?
Suddenly
What is that show host?
I'm Yura Kim
I liked the Power It item better?
Yena, the jacket is okay.
You rather than the jacket
Feeling like I'm trying to stand out more
slightly uncomfortable
Is this a networking pick?
Why did the host suddenly change?
A little more during prime time
I think I need a bike rider.
Yena, please talk to me.
Sorry, I'm a little busy.
Should I talk in front of people?
Is that okay?
Because of something
You say so?
Why are you doing this to the ethics committee?
Did you tell a ridiculous lie?
Seonmin and No PD
There's nothing between us
You know better than anyone else
What do you mean?
Are you saying it's a lie?
Of course
A feeling of not wanting to believe
I understand, but
That's all true
You're going to do this to me
I don't think so
Your desire to survive somehow
I don't know
But how can we become the same victim?
No producer trying to help Seonmin
Can you frame me?
In return for lying
Are you in prime time?
Or, I will make it a success.
Who is tricking you?
What are you talking about?
and who
Are you saying you are a victim? who?
To No PD
I don't know what I heard
I'm definitely not a victim.
prime time
With my skills and effort
I won it
Why do you guess so recklessly?
Do you insult people?
Then you
Why did you cry in front of Seonmin?
What does it mean to be so scared?
Can a senior not even visit a junior in hospital?
- Stress about everything...
- Yena!
Please be honest.
No PD help when you were new
You got a lot
When seniors vote for you
What PD Noh took care of for me
Have you already forgotten?
I'm really annoyed
no
How much help did you get?
Are you bringing up things from long ago?
Make people angry
Ha...
So
When are you coming in?
Oh, I don't know!
How many times do you say you don't know?
Not showing up to work even once
Does that make sense now?
That's up to the boss.
Why are you doing that to us?
Well, then
Just tell me where you are
I will wait and meet you
Wow, really this person
I really can't communicate.
The boss
They say they don’t want to see you.
Oh, that's it.
Stop interfering with business and leave.
I told the boss
I have something to say.
Kid! If this continues, I'm calling the police.
Get out quickly, get out!
Get out quickly
- Get out, get out.
- Just a moment.
- Get out, quickly!
- Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, get out, get out, that's enough, get out
uh
Welcome
hello
Here is President Kang Jong-ryeol
You are a member, right?
who are you?
nothing else
The store the owner often visits
It's the owner, ugh.
You suffered a trauma
You don't show up
Even though I called you
You don't even answer the phone
But you come here often, so
I wonder if we can meet
But what do I do?
how can i help you
If only Boss Kang came
Just text me once
Please add a little
I'll take care of the rest.
Ah! And
Oh, this, this, this, this
Yes
This
No, huh?
No, why just let that guy
They don't cut it, they just move it to the left.
Huh?
No, I wish I had cut it off in the first place.
Take what you can
Why are you raising your workload?
It's noisy
- Ah!
- Please don't know.
Stay still
Ah, why stay still!
uh?
No, I sold it in the first place
If you put this much
Cutting is
You shouldn't have to do it!
why those
Are you just leaving me alone?
Who do you resemble?
Is your head this bad?
what?
If you put it next to you, it won't tie your hands and feet.
Otherwise, you'll be more upset than you are now.
You don't even know how to turn your head like that?
The reason Won Bin sent me down like that now
It was too much for us.
But if you cut Jo Na-jeong in a situation like this,
Who would think that was a coincidence?
Oh, then what are you going to do? Mr.
Jo Na-jeong, that one
Are you just going to watch?
Look at that baby
Wow, it's so pretty.
Hey, if there's a girl that pretty like that
You’ll be full even if you don’t eat, right?
senior
Huh?
What are you thinking like that?
No, next item
I was wondering if there was anything interesting.
How is your married life?
Are you happy?
Why didn't I do something this good a long time ago?
I heard you think like that.
That's good
No, still, let’s move on to the next item
Is there anything interesting about marriage?
I was thinking
Oh, which one?
no
I recently got married
I heard about a couple
Is the man azoospermic?
Women go through early menopause
That's right
But give it to the other person
I'm making a confession, Mane or something like that.
You don't know because you're married
At times like this
What do you think I should do?
Uh, if you get married without confessing that.
It's a crime
- Really?
- Sure, of course.
Well, I’m saying this too
I heard it somewhere before
The man was azoospermic.
I guess they got married without telling me.
The woman found out later
This is regardless of whether you have a child or not.
They say the feeling of betrayal is no joke
I heard that’s why they got divorced.
This is a tip, sister
Want to try it with an item?
no
I'm thinking about it
I haven't decided yet
Brother, this weekend evening
Do you have time?
I have something to say
Not yet
I asked to see him too.
I also have something to say
What are you talking about?
It's no fun if you tell me in advance
I'll meet you and do it for you
See you on the weekend then
Because there is filming during the day.
Around 7pm?
Got it
What is this?
A series of late-night and early-morning broadcasts
Are you telling me to do everything for you?
That... I
I said it was too much, but
‘Skilled intern’
Why don't you use it properly and make fun of it?'
He said, and...
Now I understand
Why didn't you cut me and leave me alone?
24 hours like this
Because I'll spin it all the time
If they tease you, go out on your own feet.
Isn't it something like that?
Do you know what I'll get out of doing this?
But senior
Well, if you want to do that,
I have to go to the meeting right now.
Oh, really?
Let's go first
This is more than I thought
It's low in calories
For women controlling their weight
I think it will be very popular.
Let me emphasize that point.
Everyone, when choosing a sofa
What are you most worried about?
It's pollution.
yes, that's right
So I prepared it like this!
Even if I spill my drink like this
Sprout! Just wipe it and you're done
Because this fabric is special
It's possible
No, it's not really absorbed.
It just flows down.
Yes!
Sister, it's a meeting.
Oh, really, ugh.
Wow
Ah...
Jo Na-jeong
Are you going to do something like this?
What is this about?
Did I do something wrong?
'Did I make some mistake?'
you now
Don't you even know what you did wrong?
The show host
The face that appears on the screen
Because it’s dull sometimes
Who wants to buy your product?
That's it, Managing Director.
Now senior Joe
All broadcasts are late at night and early in the morning.
Because they are lined up
I guess it's a bit difficult
So?
It's my fault for not taking care of myself
Are you going to make an excuse for organizing the program?
If you have kids, you have kids as an excuse.
If you can't manage it, it's an excuse to organize it
This time again
What excuse are you giving?
If there are no sales, blame the product.
If the weather is nice, blame the weather
Now a fun drama
Why do you even say you don't have it?
please
If you don't have the capacity
Don't act like a fool and get out
Facial care and physical fitness management
The guy who can't do it
What did you come crawling back for?
It's all a nuisance
Still don't know?
Senior
Wait a minute
Ha...
Ah, yes, father.
Are you having a hard time? yes
I'm almost finished
Yes, I'm going now.
Najeong, I...
Well, that's not it
My cousin who lives in Gunsan
He passed away
Well, I just got a call and...
I think I should go down and have a look.
Ah... uh, yeah
I'm sure your father was very surprised.
I'll go right away then
Oh no
I'll go now, father, okay.
Now boss Kang
You came to the screen golf course.
Are you coming?
Are you here?
Wow, what does this smell like?
The visuals are awesome
Man, the taste is even better
Huh? Look, wait a minute.
Now
- What is it like? Is that right?
- hmm!
Awesome
Really awesome
So
What have you got to say?
huh? Oh no
You talk first.
Do you have something to say?
Try it first, brother.
What do you mean?
Okay, then
Uh...
Boy, originally
A little cool
I was thinking about holding an event.
Just being myself
I think it would be best
Ha... uh...
Elijah
Do you really want to marry me?
no, i
It's really a joke
I eat like this with you
We also watch TV together
Let’s take a nap together
I really, really like this time.
Yes, with that
I keep fighting with you like this
Just for life
I cook you dinner
You can just use a knee pillow because it’s comfortable.
I want to do something like that
What about you?
Not so good?
and?
Are you still
Are you not sure about me?
brother
in fact
Actually it's me
Hey, it's me
what's the matter?
- aunt!
- Minwoo, Minjun!
These guys!
Father, you are late, right?
Please go quickly
Yes, I do.
Oh my, sorry this is all late.
Oh no, old man.
You can visit with peace of mind.
is it so
Well then, please take care of me.
Listen well and play well!
- yes
Don't worry, yeah
But who is this guy?
my?
Mr. Santa sent by my mother
It's not even Christmas
Why are you Santa?
Because
Minwoo, I brought a gift for Minjun.
Wow!
Where did you get it?
I had a hamburger last time
I ordered it by mistake and it came with it.
It just occurred to me
It smells like a person
Huh?
uh? This is clearly a person
Where is it? huh?
A man with only a snot
There will be two people here
I'm going to eat you now
Where is it?
It's not here
- In here... it's here!
- Ugh!
- Here it is!
Ouch!
I have to catch it and eat it!
hello
Which room are you in?
Go straight and go to room 3...
Room 3?
- Break it?
- Yeah, just go ahead and break it.
uh, thank you
Hey, Jo Na-jeong
Huh?
Ah... yes
Hello, Director
What are you doing here?
Ah...
That...
Ugh...
Huh?
you?
Wow...
Um, Boss Kang, you lied, right?
Let's all work together
You set a trap!
How is that?
How can you treat someone like that?
Can you frame me?
- hey! hey!
- Ugh! ah!
Hey, Jo Na-jeong
You told me to go to the police today
Just by not reporting it
I know I'm lucky
Sure! Just, shit, shit.
Ouch, ah!
Brother, are you looking after the kids really well?
Did you always like kids?
Since I was young
I love the kid so much
I took care of all the neighborhood sons.
Then when you get married
Do you want to have a baby?
Hey, of course
If I had a daughter who looked like you
I really hope so
Actually
Because I am an only child
I've been very lonely since I was young.
So, when I see the family going crazy,
When I grow up and get married later,
Ah, I gave birth to two, three.
I have to live happily
I was thinking something like that
No, but what do we
It's not that I'm young
Well...
If you're wondering whether to make Ah or not
First you have to get married...
Why not?
Is it Na-jeong?
Elijah
Ah, ah, brother!
Are you here?
I'm sorry
- What about the kids?
- Kids sleep.
What are you doing in a hurry while we are here?
hey!
What's wrong with your hands?
Uh, no
Wow, really
It's absurd, it's absurd
How can humans be like that?
Are you doing something shameless?
No, then your husband
Now at Daegu Logistics Center
It's running 24 hours a day.
yes
Sorry, on a weekend evening
No, it wasn't hard for any of us.
Sang-gyu takes care of all the kids.
I just sat there
Me too really
It wasn't difficult at all, huh?
I really like my kids
Anyway thank you very much
Ah...
But
we really
Are you doing well?
I think I was too reckless
I thought it would be okay at first
I'm sure we'll get through it just fine
I thought about it
No matter what I do, I can't see the road
The company wants to catch you and kill you
Because they put pressure on me
Just tell my husband
I guess I should have said quit.
Then he and I
If both are fired from the company
At that time, the kids and I
What should I really do?
But Najeong?
Do you know what that means?
This goodness is a struggle
This dirty world
The original bad guys
It's much easier to live
But this
People who live good lives
As we continue to fight
I'm living a good life
It's just that the child survived
That much courage
I think it's amazing
In that respect, your couple
I think it's really cool
And you did it before
Even if my conscience deceives me
I won't be able to fool my children
I'm afraid my children will look like you
It was the scariest thing
That's parents
Huh?
No shame in the world
How easy is it to become a parent?
Thank you, bro.
But those people made it up
Where can I find the evidence?
No witnesses, no recordings.
There's no way to reveal anything
At the bar that the golden horses often go to
Should I plant a tape recorder?
Should I do it?
you go to the police today
Just by not reporting it
I know I'm lucky
Sure! Just, shit, shit.
Come to think of it, with President Kang
With the general manager
We rode in the car together
It's not a separate ride
Then the two of you
So you're saying we're carpooling?
Then those humans
Talking, that...
It could have been recorded on Facebook.
Yeah, that's very likely.
Hey, how do you get it out though?
A black box in someone else's car
no, no
I think there must be some way
Oh, really?
so?
The two of us play golf together
He's famous as a member who goes around fighting.
President Kang
I pick it up every time and play golf.
Drinking together
Well, I guess so.
Yeah?
Every time, President Kang leads the division.
You're saying you're going to be picked up.
That's right, that's right
Then on the block
Is there a high possibility of something happening?
Uh, baby
I know what you mean.
Well, I guess...
I went to the car and took out the memory card.
Well, you don't mean to do that, do you?
Is that a crime now?
So don't come forward
Stay still
- I'll go...
- That's it!
Is now the time for us to act boldly?
and
Compared to what those kids did
What are you going to pay for this?
Try cutting it off first.
My kids are in kindergarten
I have to take him and leave.
Baby, baby!
Ah, indeed
Now, our princes, put your socks on now.
Huh?
When did you guys wear socks like this?
Mom too
Now that you're a brother, you can't even put on socks by yourself?
Look at me too
I wore them alone
Our Minwoo and Minjun
When did you grow up like this?
It's so amazing I'm dying
Minjun
- Yes
- Mom and Dad
Much like before
Are you upset because you can’t play?
Still
For my family to be happy
I can't help it
So
Even if it's hard, just be patient
- Huh?
- Yes
Isn't it?
I like my mom's job better, right?
why?
Because mom laughs more
In the past, when I was just at home
You looked upset
When mom goes to work
I like it when you look happy
I hug you too, I hug you
My babies...
What's going on?
How have you been, Mom?
Would you be able to get along well?
I'm sorry about last time
my mom
You're so sensitive
Because of me, you became defensive.
Dear mother
I think you were being rude.
I'll apologize on your behalf
no
I didn't do anything well either.
Things to say and things to say out of excitement
It's my fault for pouring it all out, well
I also apologize to my wife...
Done
When it's all over
What good would that do?
But, mother
It's nothing else...
at first
I saw that doll
I was so surprised
So
I don't even think about finding out more
Start by getting angry at Sangmin.
I think I decided arbitrarily.
So I asked Sangmin.
They never told me anything.
Because it’s frustrating
Even to my mother like this
I came to ask a question.
You know, mother, right?
What kind of doll is that?
yes
They
what you imagine
They're not those weird kids
when i was young
It's a mannequin used in a dressmaker's shop.
I gave up my business and had nowhere else to put it.
I left it in the basement.
The only thing Sangmin didn't say was
I didn't even think about it
Actually
Sangmin's father
People can't communicate
I had very bad hand habits.
Dad!
Please!
Oh, please!
Yes, keep crying! Like that, huh?
Whenever a boy does something, he gets upset.
I told you not to do that
How many times do I talk to you? seed
honey!
What is it? uh? Come out!
you to your child
Because it wraps around like that
The kid looks like this
It's not like this!
Better, kill me!
Better kill me!
Ouch! Mr.
Dad, please save me
Please!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You're not right yet
Huh? Come here
Come on, let’s hit you first.
- Mom, Mom!
- Come here! Mr.
- Honey, honey!
- mom!
- Mom, Mom!
honey!
- Come here!
- dad!
dad!
If you do it casually
A boy like a girl
I feel like crying
I spanked my child so often.
Wow!
Mom...
In the end, after thinking about it,
I...
Sangmin
You were very scared, right?
These guys
They're not scary kids
A guardian angel who protects you
Angel?
Their names are
It's Rebecca and Jessica...
Rebecca
Jessica
Angel?
Yeah
Don't get bored
I gave the mannequin a name
Rebecca and Jessica
Then
From then on, even if I'm trapped there
There was no crying sound
It's all my fault
We should have split up a long time ago
After going to the dressmaker's shop once,
I have no confidence in earning a living.
Even if my dad is a bit of a bitch
Rather than having nothing
I endured it because I thought it would get better.
Sangmin continues like that.
I never thought I would be obsessed with them
I never even dreamed of it
I told you too
The reason why I kept being anxious to have a child
Who said that
The love I didn't receive from my parents
If you love your child to the fullest,
It gets better naturally
Youngah Joo
I'm sorry
I was too young back then
Divorce was a sin in those days.
I didn't even know what a mother was like.
I was so foolish
no, i
There's a barrier in my heart
It seems like there is
I feel sorry for myself
Oh, no!
- Drop this!
- Oh, no, no!
It hurts, really!
Let go!
Rebecca
Rebecca!
Taejeong!
- Go first.
- Yes
I have a favor to ask.
No, well, on the agenda for today’s meeting
Is there anything else you want to say?
None
No, please speak comfortably.
- I don't think there's more.
- I don't think there is one.
Okay, then today's meeting is
That's it for now
- Thank you for your hard work.
Yeah
Until 11am tomorrow morning
Pick up in front of my house
You cracked the obi twice like you did back then.
Make triple bogey
Huh? Then
You pay the green fee
Okay, see you tomorrow, okay.
They say they're going to play golf tomorrow.
Usually, after the two of us finish playing golf,
A bar I always stop by
Polyamorous
This is a private bar?
If you leave at 11am
Tee-off usually at 1pm
Until about 5 o'clock
After washing up and eating dinner, uh...
Probably around 7 or 8 o'clock here
I think it will arrive
Okay, okay.
President Kang’s car
Large SUV from L company, gray.
what?
- 4534
Okay, just a moment.
Is it valet?
Oh no
I'm waiting too
Ah...
Where have you gone?
- Did you call the assistant manager?
- Oh, yeah.
-What is your number...
- 5478
5478, 5478
yes
Ah... Ugh!
This is Seongdam-dong 12-5.
Jinja Apartment in Donhyeon-dong
40,000 won?
yes, okay
yes, quickly
yes
Did you call a substitute?
uh?
I just called you
It's coming this quickly?
It was right nearby
Huh?
no way...
Ugh... Ugh!
Ugh!
The car...
- Oh my, oh my.
- Oh my!
Ah...
Ah, why is this happening?
How many times do I say I don't like it?
What do you hate?
Stop bouncing now
Let’s date me officially, okay?
Oh, I hate it, really!
- Ah...
-Mr...
Why are you bouncing like this? Mr.
Huh?
Take everything you get, Mr.
Wow
Ah, President Kang!
I have a drink with Yena
I'll do more, so go first
Yeah, have a good time.
Uh, I hope, okay, go.
Donhyeon-dong!
What are you doing when you’re not going?
Boss, fasten your belts.
Ugh!
It's Yena
Drop me off, I want to go home.
Hey, it's Yena
Oh, really, why are you like this?
Hey, Song Yena
You have a secret closet
Did you think it was free?
prime time
Did you plan to just take it and eat it?
Let's go in a good mood
Huh?
Driver, please go quickly.
Hey, what are you doing now?
Don't you drive properly?
It's noisy!
It's crazy, so shut your mouth!
cadet!
What are you really doing?
uh?
What are you doing now?
Sorry, sir.
Yena, get down!
Hey, Jo Na-jeong
What are you doing now?
Are you crazy?
The general manager is
What are you doing now?
What are you doing?
What about a boss and subordinates?
Can't you have a drink?
Can’t we take a taxi together?
Hey, Boss Kang!
I, Mr.
- Let's go
- Oh, hey!
Hey, Song Yena, you talk about it.
Boy, did I drag you by force?
Because you asked me to have another drink
I'm not gone!
Talk to me quickly!
That's right
The general manager forced
It’s true that you dragged him away!
I say I don't like it but I force it
It's true that it was burned!
Why do you keep flirting with me even though I don’t like it?
I clearly said I didn't like it
Why do you keep
I'm messing around here and there
You bastard!
Hey
Ouch! Mr.
Hey, Jo Na-jeong!
Now
Oh no
That's right, those people call
Why do you go out drinking?
If it seems like such a dangerous place
I shouldn't have gone out at all
Over and over again
I gave it prime time
He said he didn’t even come to say hello.
Because they keep berating me for being ungrateful.
Because I’m really embarrassed too
Ah, indeed
now what am i saying
You understand clearly, right?
Is it poop or soybean paste?
Shouldn’t you try it, you idiot?
But
Why were you there all of a sudden?
Those kids are no PDs
I was framed, so I went looking for evidence.
But
Kim Jeong-sik's older sister's face
I've seen it all, what should I do?
What can't I do?
Hey, that's right
You're being dragged like that
Are you going to leave me alone and go home?
ah! I really
My nose is three feet long
I missed all the evidence because of this nonsense!
Who should I blame?
Are you sober?
I'm going in first, be careful
Sister, just for today
Can't I let you sleep at my sister's house?
- uh?
- I guess I live alone.
I'm scared that Kim Jeong-sik will come looking for me.
Then I really don't think I can handle it.
But sleeping at work doesn’t mean
It's scarier
sit, sit
The house is small, so there is no separate room for me.
you sleep in bed
Because of the kids
I have to go back and forth often.
thank you
Oh my, I'm dying
Oh my, I'm dying!
Wow, what an action movie
I made a fuss like someone who filmed me
My whole body aches, it's just
Ah, ah...
Well...
Don't think about anything for now
sleep well
When I wake up from some sleep
My complicated mind will be sorted out.
Oh no
Put out the fire?
sleep well
What does that mean?
What is Jo Na-jeong looking at?
I'm out, I'm out
Ah...
So, how did this happen?
Me, Kang Jong-ryeol, and Song Ye-na
Have a drink
Song Ye-na and I
I'm taking a taxi
No, where did it come from?
Jo Na-jeong appears
You're dragging Song Yena with you.
Why did you summon Song Yena?
Why on earth is Song Yena again?
No, I have no idea
It didn't happen
Because we are in the same boat
I meant to be friendly
Are you human?
How did I stop you!
How did I stop it!
What are you going to do? uh?
What are you going to do now?
Hey, you crazy bastard!
Kyungseon...
Ah, really, why am I like this?
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it was because I was lonely too!
you me
Because I hate it so much and ignore it
It's because I'm upset too.
Ah...
Kyungseon-ah
Please save me just once
Because I really won't make that mistake again
please
Ah, really, why am I like this? really
Ugh, Ugh, Ugh, really
Yes, but these days, food disposers
There are so many different types.
What's different?
That's right
Well, the basics are obvious.
But Irven is more than that.
Because we used to
No matter how much I change the filter
There was a time when it smelled
Is that because of the inner tube?
If the inner pipe is not dried,
There was a time when it smelled
But Irben
This product solves that problem.
Food...
Why?
Can't sleep?
Should I give you some honey water?
No
It's okay
sister
I'm really sorry
me
I wanted to succeed
So then
Even though I know it won’t work
Kim Jeong-sik, even when that bastard was being aggressive.
I just stayed still
Even when Managing Director Seo tells me to shut up
I stayed still
When Seonmin became like that
It was so painful
You just have to endure it and pass by.
Then it becomes nothing
Just pass by
pass by
I was closing my eyes and ears like that.
Now those bastards
He used that as an excuse to tell me
They even make you lie.
That's what my sister said
I thought it was a poisonous vessel too
It was so sweet
Prime time my whole life
When will you try it?
If you miss this opportunity
I will never get another chance
Because I think so
A shameless lie came out.
sister
If I reveal the truth
You will be buried out of the industry, right?
But if you don't reveal it
In the end, to Kim Jeong-sik
It will continue to happen like this
It's all my fault
Even if I didn’t close my eyes
To Kim Jeong-sik
Even if I didn't try to look good
Managing Director
Oh, yes, Najeong.
Maybe yes...
Are you at home?
yes
Uh, yeah
What is Yena
I think I'm misunderstanding
I called but you didn't answer
Because I’m not even at home
For some reason, it felt like I was with you.
I'm sorry
Yeah, kinda...
Can you tell me to come out?
no
Yena, the reason we’re not seeing each other now is because
I think it would be good
Yeah...
I understand
But you too
I hope you don't misunderstand
The general manager really likes people.
There is an innocent corner
I am often misunderstood
This time, I really want to have a drink with Yena.
He said he just called me out...
Really to you
What I want to say is
This incident...
If you just close your eyes
The contract you wanted so badly
I'll do it right away, even tomorrow.
Wonbin will also be reinstated immediately.
you
here so desperately
You wanted to come back
If you close your eyes just once
your whole life like that
The show host I wanted to be
I can continue
Besides, you're good at it, right?
brand with your name
There’s no law saying you shouldn’t launch it.
Stop it now, Mr.
At this point, the managing director
Please from the general manager
Shouldn’t you get away?
This girl, that girl
People who accumulate
It's my husband
How long are you going to protect me?
Managing Director, you weren’t really this kind of person.
Colder than anyone else
He was a just man.
Managing Director, you said that when I was new.
Just give me an hour and end it
It may be a broadcast, but
To partners
It's an hour where the fate of the company depends.
So
Time that took someone else's life
Don't even think about doing it.
From then on
I respected and liked the manager.
for a long time
I wanted to be like you, Mr.
The person who said that...
Why have you changed like this?
You're the kid's dad...
You are also a mother of children.
Don't you understand?
Even if I become a wreck
Even if my heart is torn apart by shame
my daughter...
The child of a molester
I couldn't let it happen
The mother was trying to protect her daughter
Is it so wrong?
I lived really hard
For my daughter, for my family
Really hard...
That's really for my daughter
Was it a choice?
Honestly, Mr.
Didn’t you want to succeed?
Rather, your daughter
You may have been distressed
To protect such a father
Looking at my mom
Even now
I admired
As the managing director at that time
Could you please come back?
Because of some symptoms
Is that so?
A while ago I
I was diagnosed with early menopause.
That's just one hospital
I've been there
I was wondering if it was a misdiagnosis...
and
bleeding a while ago
It was a little bit transparent, but
That's why I got my period
I might have mistakenly thought I didn't do it.
Um... then
Shall we take a look at the ultrasound first?
yes
Um...
Unfortunately,
It's not a misdiagnosis
On ultrasound examination
Menopause seems certain
At the former hospital
Did you have your FSH levels tested?
yes
Blood is briefly visible for a moment
It may occur when you are tired or
This is a temporary phenomenon
Are you taking your medicine well?
- No
- Uh, you can't do that.
If you don't take medicine
can't sleep
Your body feels feverish
Are you experiencing menopausal symptoms?
I hope you take your medicine regularly.
I recommend it
Don't skip meals
Condition management
It's important to be nice
Didn’t Jooyoung get off work?
I'm late because I'm working overtime today.
Ah
Didn't you eat dinner?
I bought this pig's trotters and soju.
Wow, I'm already hungry
I was just thinking about getting something to eat.
What is this?
Hey, where are you hurting?
Ah...
no
It's not painful
I'm a little tired
I bought some vitamins
Oh, is that right?
These days, vitamins even have the days of the week written on them.
That's right
Let's eat first
I
Don't be so nervous and come out of nowhere
How many times did I say it?
Ugh?
No, I...
Then in front of me
The person fell asleep
Are you still? I need to help
Hey, why are you crying?
Just...
Because the movie is sad
like that
It's not a sad movie
strange
I'm sad
It's so sad
Why am I like this?
Ilya, is it your day? uh?
Me, I don’t really know.
Girls become a little more sensitive on those days
I heard that's just the way it is, don't you know?
I guess so
I guess it's that day
But of course
If that's the case...
Oh, my goodness
I don’t know how to do it, I don’t know how to do it
It's a hit, it's a hit
This is Jo Na-jeong, intern.
Please sit down
Are you going to recant your testimony?
yes
Actually
Kim Seon-min, show host
Producer Wonbin Now is
There is no relationship
Yes?
Then what about what you stated last time?
tell you here
I'm so sorry but
I gave false testimony that day.
With Director Kim Jeong-sik
Director Seo’s
Due to coercive threats and appeasement
I made a mistake
Our ethics committee testimony
A major turmoil within the company
evoked
The testimony of a decisive witness
It was overturned
Additional circumstances of sexual harassment were also revealed.
Accordingly, all members of our ethics committee
with unanimous opinion
Director Kim Jeong-sik was dismissed.
Notice
Director Kim Jeong-sik
Internal sexual harassment department
In the name of unfair behavior in the workplace
was suddenly dismissed
Mr. Managing Director
Take responsibility for all of this
submitted my resignation
in the end
A decision is made to reinstate the husband.
Everything goes back to its place
It seemed like he came back, but
unexpectedly
shocked us all
the ugly truth
It was revealed again
Hey, Jo Na-jeong
Did you hear that?
what? What are you talking about?
Kim Jeong-sik and President Kang
He said he was caught at the police station.
Why?
For what reason?
Managing Director
Oh, Managing Director, Managing Director
Managing Director, Managing Director, Managing Director
Uh, uh!
Managing Director
Managing Director, are you okay?
But
It didn't end there
me again
The misfortune that tries to hit me from behind
had to face it
What does that mean?
Among our interns
Who might get fired?
no, i did this morning
In the break room
I heard the general affairs team talking among themselves.
- Uh
- But
We have a total of seven interns.
But what are you applying for next month?
How come only six people apply?
Well, they said that
So, maybe
Who among us gets cut off?
I'm anxious because I wonder if it's there
Ha!
What are you going to do?
Are you just going to suffer like this?
No, why?
Why bother getting involved in other people’s business?
Severely cut off from the company?
I'll pack my bags by today
I'm leaving so come right in
Hey, Sangmin!
Would you like to eat ramen?
What kind of trip is a trip in this situation?
Oooooh!
So good!
What happened?
Giving birth to a daughter who looks like me
I look at you with earnest eyes and say it’s a wish.
How can I say that?
briefly during the day
The kid who went out to get some air
I still can't contact you
Illy!
What is that?